

(a) 01 September 1993

Q Cairo, Egypt

01200355945

011152095075

mohamedElbyaa100@gmail.com

### EDUCATION

May 2018

**EELU** 

Faculty of Computer Science And Artificial Intelligent

### SKILLS

- User Interface
- User Experience
- Wire-framing & Prototyping
- Design system
- User Researcher
- Usability testing
- information Architecture
- Product Design
- information Architecture

#### **Technical**

- Figma
- Adobe XD
- Hotjar
- Google Analytics

# mohamed nageh elbyaa

Product designer

### ABOUT

Digital Products Designer (UI/UX) with 4 years of experience, worked for Various agencies and startups and has built a wide range of projects web and mobile for clients from Egypt, Germany and KSA, I am excited to contribute my expertise to projects that challenge me and allow me to make a meaningful difference in the world of design and make a tangible impact by creating products that not only meet user needs but also push the boundaries of innovation.

#### EXPERIENCE

Saudi Arabia (Remote)

2022 - Present

#### Antilla

Product Designer (Full Time)

- Collaborate with product managers to translate business objectives and requirements into great UX and UI.
- Lead projects through the full design process, from early ideas and sketches to wireframes and prototypes
- Led brainstorming sessions to facilitate new ideas for product improvement
- Negotiated with stakeholders and developers to find the balance between user needs and business objectives.
- Build a New Design System Help My Teamwork smooth & Easier & Efficient

2 mobile app 5 Web app 2 dashboard

Germany(Remote)

2020 - 2022

## **Springyunivers**

Ui/Ux Designer (Full Time)

- Worked on various projects for clients from different industries, ranging from ecommerce to mobile apps.
- Designed interactive prototypes for client presentations and user testing.
- Collaborated with clients to refine designs and deliver high-quality results.

1 VR 6 mobile app 3 Web app 3 dashboard

Egypt(On Site)

2019 - 2020

# Corptia

Ui/Ux Designer (Full Time)

- Designing solutions for web, mobile, and tablet applications.
- Create assets across all of our channels: app, web, display, social, and other digital touchpoint.
- Designing layout and revising deliverables using established style guides, templates, and branding guidelines.
- Communicating design ideas and prototypes to developers

6 mobile app 2 Web app 3 dashboard